Billy Campagnoli

Teléfono +584140271179 Email: Bjcampagnoli@gmail.com

PROFILE

Dedicated virtual advisor in different business areas, I have vast experience in dealing with people, I am polite, courteous and empathetic. I am a proactive person with the desire to learn and improve myself. The work I do I do it with responsibly giving the best.

WORK EXPERIENCE

Date: Mar 2021 - to date

Place: Santa Teresa del Tuy, State. Miranda, Venezuela

Job: Virtual Assistant

Company: Jhonny Escalante Soluciones SRL

Description of Activities: Virtual Advice to clients that includes:

• Answer questions about an article or project.

• Schedule visits to different locations of urban projects

• Channel complaints to the corresponding departments

Date: Mar 2019 — Jul 2020

Place: Santa Teresa del Tuy, State. Miranda, Venezuela

Job: Refrigeration Technician

Company: Tecnionza GM. C.A.

Description of Activities: Review and maintenance, which included cleaning, of industrial refrigeration equipment with a capacity of more than 30 Tons. of refrigeration. I also assisted my superiors in the placement of new equipment and other maintenance in the electrical area, of which I have an average experience.

SKILLS

o Collaboration and teamwork

o Strong communication skills

o Data Analysis Skills

o Creativity

o Ability to Learn

o Analysis and Troubleshooting

EDUCATION

Period: Sep. 2011 — Sep. 2016

Institution: Simón y Simón Educational Unit

Degree Obtained: Bachelor of Science

Period: Mar 2017 — Mar 2019

Institution: Universidad Nacional Experimental Politécnica "Luis Caballero Mejías" (UNEXPO)

Núcleo Charallave

Pensum corresponding to a year and a half of the career of Superior Technician in Civil

Construction approved.

Pensum corresponding to two semesters of the approved Higher Technical Career in Electricity.

LANGUAGES

Average command of English

Basic Command of Italian

COURSES

Period: Mar 2020 — Oct 2020 (Completed)

Title: Refrigeration Maintenance

Institution: Educational Unit in Fe y Alegría

Period: Feb 2019 — Aug. 2020 (Completed Level I,II)

Denomination: Basic Italian

Institution: National Institute of Italian Culture